http://www.infotoday.eu/privacy.aspx#cookies

This website uses cookies to improve your user experience. By continuing to use this site you consent to the use of cookies on your device, as described in our cookie policy. Parts of this website may not work as expected without cookies. To find out more about cookies, including how to manage and delete them, visit www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org.
Home
Features
News
Blog
Press Releases
View Press Releases
Submit a Press Release
Newsletter
PRIVACY NOTICE
This privacy notice explains how Information Today Ltd uses any personal information we collect about you. Information Today Ltd is a sister company of Information Today Inc.
What information do we collect about you?
How will we use the information about you?
Marketing
Access to your information
Cookies
Changes to our privacy notice
How to contact us
What information do we collect about you?
We collect information about you when you express your interest in, or sign up for, our conferences, publications and other resources we provide. We also collect information when you complete customer surveys, provide feedback, and participate in competitions. Website usage information is collected using cookies. We only hold information that you have submitted to us: this generally includes your full name, business or personal mailing address, email address, telephone number, and sometimes demographic information that you have provided (for example, the industry you work in, your job function, and so on).
How will we use the information about you?
If you sign up for a conference, or subscribe to a publication or enewsletterWe collect information about you to process your conference registration or other purchase/subscription, or to manage your account and, if you agree, to email you about related products and services we think may be of interest to you. We may share your information with sister Information Today companies so that they may offer you related products and services. We do not sell or pass on your information to third parties.
If you are attending a conference, we may also send you information about the conference sponsors, but only if you have given permission for us to do so.
If you register to view/download premium content on one of our websitesIf you sign up for premium content such as online events (webinars), or White Papers we may also share your information with the sponsors so that they may extend you offers of interest.
If you request information about sponsorship or advertising If you enquire about sponsorship or advertising opportunities at our conferences or in our publications or websites, we may send you further information about these opportunities (eg Media Kit or Invitation to Sponsor) and your details may be shared with Information Today’s sales representative.
Marketing
We will send you information about the products and services you have enquired about, and we would like to send you information about other Information Today products and services which may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving this information at any time, by emailing info.uk@infotoday.com.
Please note that, if you opt out of receiving information from us, this may prevent you from receiving important conference or related information.In some cases we use legitimate interest as a lawful basis for processing your data. We define ‘legitimate interest’ as contacting you to draw your attention to new editions of products and services you have bought or enquired about in the past, or to draw your attention to related products and services that we provide.
Access to your information
You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please email info.uk@infotoday.com or write to us at: The Data Protection Officer, Information Today Ltd, Henderson House, Hithercroft Road, Wallingford, Oxon OX10 8LD, UK.
We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information.
If you don’t wish to receive notifications and offers from us, you can request to be removed from our mailing lists. Every email message sent to mailing lists maintained by Information Today contains a link to automatically unsubscribe from the list, or lists, to which the email was sent.
Cookies
Cookies are small text files, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that are sent to your computer or other access devices from our servers, or from the servers of our third party partners. Cookies are placed on your computer to collect internet log information and visitor behaviour information. This information is used to track visitor use of our websites and to compile statistical reports on website activity. Information on how you can delete, disable, or control cookies for most web browsers is available at www.allaboutcookies.org or www.aboutcookies.org. If you choose to do so, in a few cases some of our website features may not function as a result.
The various Information Today websites use different types of cookies:
Our websites that offer access to White Papers, Webinars, and other premium content and online events use cookies to store registration information, so that website visitors are remembered, and do not need to supply that information upon each visit.
Information Today also uses certain third-party partner companies that also send cookies to your computer/device via your web browser:
We use Google Analytics, a popular web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. Google Analytics uses cookies to count the number of visitors to our websites, and helps us to analyse how users use our websites. It tells us things such as the typical length of stay on the site or the average number of pages a user views. User data is all anonymous.
You can find out more about Google’s position on privacy as regards its analytics service at http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html
We use Google's DoubleClick for Publishers to serve ads on our websites. These cookies are very similar to the Google Analytics cookie described above, but are specific to the display of advertising on our websites. User data is anonymous.
Google AdSense cookies are used by Google to report to us how certain ads shown on our websites are performing. User data is all anonymous.
You can find out more generally about Google and its policies and principles as regards advertising at http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/
Changes to our privacy notice
We keep our privacy notice under regular review and we will place any updates on this web page. This privacy notice was last updated on 10 October 2019.
How to contact us
Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy notice or information we hold about you. You can contact us by:
Email:
info.uk@infotoday.com
Telephone:
+44 (0)7510 729377
Post:
Data Protection OfficerInformation Today LtdHenderson HouseHithercroft RoadWallingfordOxon OX10 8LD, UK
Connect with InfoToday Europe
@IntLibIntl
Newsletters
Email:
Most Popular
WIPO Launches New Free Database of Judicial Decisions on Intellectual Property from Around the World
Moody's Buys Acquire Media: New Perspectives for News Aggregators
Educational Publishers Obtain Preliminary Injunction Against 63 Illegal eBook Websites that Use Online Ads to Sell Pirated Content
Launch of the OAPEN Open Access Books Toolkit
Landmark analysis by Elsevier maps research data as UN Sustainable Development Goals reach fifth anniversary
News and ideas for, and by, innovative info pros from around the world, throughout the year - #ili365
Join us 13-14 October 2020, Olympia, London – the face-to-face place for innovative info pros - #ili2020
© 2000 - 2020, Information Today LTD, an Information Today (ITI) company.
[Privacy/Cookies Policy]
